KUMMARI TIRUPATHI RAO

Andhra Pradesh, India



tirupathi9436@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/kummari-tirupathi-rao-290b65161

Summary

Worked as a C# developer for 2.5 years.

Strong command of the C, C# and C++ programming languages as well as the Unity game engine.

Contributed to a Unity project for a video game that had more than 1 lakh downloads.

I am a team player and am an efficient communicator. I'm currently looking for employment in a game development studio as a game programmer.

Experience



RRR The Game Ride Race Rescue

SK-GAMES

Sep 2022 - Jan 2023 (5 months)

I have contributed to the RRR game project.

RRR-The Game is a third-person Racing Adventure Game, where you can choose to play as Ram or Bheem. Race against time to save the boy who is trapped under the bridge because of a massive fire accident caused by a derailed freight train.

Competencies:

C# Unity for Game Development

ProBuilder and UModeler for Game Modelling/Designing

Associate Consultant

Capgemini

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

- Demonstrated experience and good hands-on programming experience C#.
- Key contributor in the design and implementation of new features.

Senior Analyst

Capgemini

Sep 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 4 months)

• Machine Learning Intern

Hivericks Technologies Pvt Ltd

May 2019 - Jul 2019 (3 months)

- Internship at Hivericks Technologies Private Limited, Chennai.
- Implemented a machine learning model to predict battery discharge rate based on user usage patterns.

Education

National Institute of Technology Meghalaya

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electronics and Communications Engineering 2016 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

- ★ Unity Junior Programmer Unity
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals Microsoft 1395-5733
- Associate Innovator Capgemini
- AWS Game Day Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Skills

C# • Unity • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Oracle SQL Developer • Data Structures • Algorithms • Microsoft Azure • Agile Methodologies • Adobe Photoshop • After Effects

Honors & Awards

Young Emerging Professional - Capgemini
Dec 2022